<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<LanguageData>

  <!-- Syndicate -->

  <Apparello_Syndicatellorare.label>кардинал страника</Apparello_Syndicatellorare.label>
  <Apparello_Syndicatellorare.description>Lone wanderers would wear something like this while on their noble crusade or vendetta.</Apparello_Syndicatellorare.description>


  <!-- Scyther -->

  <Apparello_Scytherframe.label>прототип scyther frame</Apparello_Scytherframe.label>
  <Apparello_Scytherframe.description>Mobility enhancing wireframe based on inner workings of a mechanoid 'scyther' unit. Warning! Due to awkward adaptation to human bodystructure long usage may cause major muscle strains.
Wearer may be rendered susceptible to unwanted side-effects. Including but not limited to: Complete loss of motor functions, Motion sickness, and nose bleed.</Apparello_Scytherframe.description>


  <!-- Hive -->

  <Apparello_HiveArmor.label>прототип брони улья</Apparello_HiveArmor.label>
  <Apparello_HiveArmor.description>Fashioned after the centipede bodystructure. This extremely bulky armor is nigh indestructable. The Sheer weight of this piece of armor drastically hinders mobility</Apparello_HiveArmor.description>


  <!-- Steamhull -->

  <Apparello_Steamhull.label>прототип steamhull</Apparello_Steamhull.label>
  <Apparello_Steamhull.description>Combination of mobility enhancing components of the Scyther frame and heavy plating of the Hive armor.
The increased energy consumption from the added scyther frame servos, have forced the shock dampeners work on lesser capacity,
thus rendering the wearer more vulnerable to injuries but the higher mobility under combat situations are well worth it. Generates absurd amounts of heat though.</Apparello_Steamhull.description>


  <!-- Medium power -->

  <Apparello_GShellII.label>медицинская силовая броня</Apparello_GShellII.label>
  <Apparello_GShellII.description>Powered medium armor, designed for combat medics. Comes with attached GlitOrion© hip'n'hop™ thrusters and StimulantPak™ for faster mobility and healing</Apparello_GShellII.description>


</LanguageData>