<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<LanguageData>

  <!-- Doom, Doom marine -->

  <Apparello_Doom.label>шлем десантника</Apparello_Doom.label>
  <Apparello_Doom.description>The B4D-455 class infantry helmet used by the marines during the incident at the Mars science facility. The production of these were since discontinued. A real relic of distant past</Apparello_Doom.description>


  <!-- Cave Story (Doukutsu Monogatari), Quote -->

  <Apparello_Quote.label>war-engineer's comm-link</Apparello_Quote.label>
  <Apparello_Quote.description>Often referred to as redcaps. The war-engineers were in charge of keeping the supply lines up and running. 
There's stories of one heroic Forward scout war-engineer crashlanding on a tunnelworld during a war in the local star system.. 
Said engineer eventually escaped the planet after somehow managing to activate a nuclear device in the planet's core, which left the planet uninhabitable. 

It is not known whether his tale of the Tunnelworld being under dictatorship of a powerhungry scientist was true or not.
The ramblings about speedrunning through hell with his girlfriend on tow was big blow on his credibility.

Only confirmed truth in whole story is that the tunnelworld did indeed blow up!
	</Apparello_Quote.description>


  <!-- Borderlands, Psycho -->

  <Apparel_Psymask.label>psy co. противогаз™</Apparel_Psymask.label>
  <Apparel_Psymask.description>The Psy company's gasmask™ has to be their most profiting product of all times. 
It's built in vision sensor technology allowed the wearer to operate in thickest of toxic clouds and more importantly, survive.</Apparel_Psymask.description>


  <!-- Zorro, Zorro -->

  <Apparello_Zorro.label>шляпа и маска страника</Apparello_Zorro.label>
  <Apparello_Zorro.description>This apparel is fashioned after the famed hat used by the legendary vigilante El Fox - 'En garde, noble foe! You cannot avoid justice- The vigilante justice!'</Apparello_Zorro.description>


  <!-- Turtles, Footclan -->

  <Apparello_Footy.label>метка клана балаклава</Apparello_Footy.label>
  <Apparello_Footy.description>Without proper methods of finding out, You'll be forever uncertain whether this balaclava is the real deal or not. The marking on the forehead strongly suggests it indeed is a remnant of the ancient clan of pugilists</Apparello_Footy.description>


  <!-- Mass Effect, Tali Zorah -->

  <Apparello_Meffect.label>причудливый головной убор</Apparello_Meffect.label>
  <Apparello_Meffect.description>Warm and cozy and most importantly airtight headgear designed for deep-space explorers to combat the hostile bacteria on uninhabitable planets.</Apparello_Meffect.description>


  <!-- cowless -->

  <Apparello_Meffectwo.label>причудливый головной убор2</Apparello_Meffectwo.label>
  <Apparello_Meffectwo.description>Mostly airtight headgear designed for deep-space explorers to combat the hostile bacteria on uninhabitable planets.</Apparello_Meffectwo.description>


  <!-- MDK, Kurt Hectic -->

  <Apparello_Kurt.label>aerocowl MkII</Apparello_Kurt.label>
  <Apparello_Kurt.description>The ingenious aerodynamic miracle by Kurtech. It's not really a cowl anymore but at this point it's too late to rename it.</Apparello_Kurt.description>

  <Apparello_Kurtlite.label>aerocowl</Apparello_Kurtlite.label>
  <Apparello_Kurtlite.description>The ingenious aerodynamic miracle by Kurtech.</Apparello_Kurtlite.description>


  <!-- Mega Man, Mega Man -->

  <Apparello_Rockman.label>Шлем пилота</Apparello_Rockman.label>
  <Apparello_Rockman.description>All the famous shuttle pilots wore one of these, some were more adorned than others. This is one of the more practical and basic ones.</Apparello_Rockman.description>


  <!-- Mad Max beyond thuderdome, Raider -->

  <Apparello_Raideroos.label>маска обмана</Apparello_Raideroos.label>
  <Apparello_Raideroos.description>Something pulled seemingly straight out of junkyard. It has it's own kind of charm to it</Apparello_Raideroos.description>


  <!-- League of Legends, Master Yi (Close enough, anyway) -->

  <Apparello_Yi.label>Головной убор infiltrator</Apparello_Yi.label>
  <Apparello_Yi.description>Equipped with very intricate target tracking system and pathing analyzer. The headgear was very popular among assassins and spies of all kinds. It's a real shame the type of batteries used in this haven't been manufactured in decades. However! someone has rigged this thing up to power from kinetic dynamo</Apparello_Yi.description>


  <!-- Psychonauts, Razputin -->

  <Apparello_Raz.label>шляпа художника</Apparello_Raz.label>
  <Apparello_Raz.description>Hardened leather and snazzy goggles. it's almost as if you could pilot your way through someone's psyche with this cap equipped!</Apparello_Raz.description>


</LanguageData>