<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<ModMetaData>
  <name>VGP Vegetable Garden</name>
  <author>dismarzero</author>
  <packageId>dismarzero.VGP.VGPVegetableGarden</packageId>
  <url>https://ludeon.com/forums/index.php?topic=36926.0</url>
<supportedVersions>
	<li>1.3</li>
</supportedVersions>  
  <incompatibleWith>
  <li>FrozenSnowFox.GrowableGrass</li>
  </incompatibleWith>
<description>
Vegetable Garden 


Hello! And welcome to the vegetable garden! 

One of the oldest mods for the Rim.


Vegetable Garden:

The main piece of my new project! Will have smaller bits of other mods built in. 

But tried keep the size down and still keep the spirit of the garden when used alone.

Tier Crop Growth:
Starter Crops
-potatoes - grows well anywhere
-corn - long growing with high yields
-rice - fast growing
-barley - immune to blight and used to make tea and ale. 

Tier 1 research "special property plants"
-snow beats - grows well anywhere, does not die from cold snaps
-lentils - meat substitute
-beans - many uses in the gourmet garden
-Olives - does not destroy plant when harvest, yield after first is faster

Tier 2 research fruits
-watermelon, grapes, blueberries, strawberries, agave

Tier 3 research fruit trees
-Apples, Bananas, Oranges, Peaches

Wild plants:
-Apples, Cherries, Bananas, Coconuts, Dates, Figs, Pineapple, Cloudberries, Gooseberries. 
-Mushrooms found in any wet biome. Can be used as a meat substitute.
-Bee Hives that produce honey.

-Hydroponic:
Corn, Devilstrand, Hay grass, Ambrosia, and Baby agarilux (cave mushroom).

Bee trees can be research to grow honey.

Ingredients Plants:
-Coffee and Tea

Wood:
-Bamboo fast growing wood
-Ironwood very beautiful but for crafting and building, not for fuel

You can convert Ironwood and Bamboo to wood at the stonecutter's table.

Defence Plants:
-Tall Grass
-Choke vine

Other Features:
-Grow-able Grass
-Silage Animal Feed
-Bulk Recipes : Kibble
-Stir-Fry and Stew Recipes with added meal effects.
-Hardtack vegetable style Pemmican biscuit. 
-New Categories for stockpiles.
-Coffee, Tea, Mead,barley tea, chocolate milk, and Fruit Drink.
-Bio-Fuel: fuel for fueled tables.
-New Flower: Plumeria
-New Tree: Ironwood and Bamboo.
-New Floors for bamboo, ironwood.
-Convert Ironwood and Bamboo to Wood at the stone-cutting table.
-2x2 Food Shelf with perishable stockpile already set up.

-Art work by Spoonshortage and Crusty Peanut.


Custom Tribal Start notes / Known Issues:
If you are trying to use the Scenario Editor for any Custom Tribal added by any mod other then the Core game you will get a tons of errors.

You can still play these, just not edit them. And It will just throw two harmless RED errors at start and the rest of the game plays fine.
More info on this here:
http://bit.ly/2VO1thp
 
Steam and Downloads on the forum page will always only contain the newest Game version of my mods. Meaning currently 1.1 mods. I will not be supporting older versions of my mods as most players will likely move up to the new version on new games. I do keep the last stable version of each version of the game on my Nexus mods page. And 1.0 mods can be found on my Dropbox account. 
Forum:
http://bit.ly/3a1Q6GE
Dropbox 1.0
http://bit.ly/2T8tJZj
Nexus mods:
http://bit.ly/2PlLSBB
Vegetable Garden Project Steam Home and Credits page:
http://bit.ly/38W0TC6
Mod Compitiblity Patch List:
http://bit.ly/2HRyzEV


 </description>



</ModMetaData>



