<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" ?>
<Defs>
	<HugsLib.UpdateFeatureDef Abstract="true" Name="UpdateFeatureBase">
		<modNameReadable>Giddy-up Battle Mounts</modNameReadable>
		<modIdentifier>BattleMounts</modIdentifier>
		<linkUrl>https://ludeon.com/forums/index.php?topic=37323</linkUrl>
	</HugsLib.UpdateFeatureDef>
	<HugsLib.UpdateFeatureDef ParentName="UpdateFeatureBase">
		<defName>BattleMounts_0_18_3</defName>
		<assemblyVersion>0.18.3</assemblyVersion>
		<content>Giddy-up Battle Mounts has been updated with the following changes: 
- Enemy pawns now also use mounts during raids and ambushes!
- The chance that a given enemy pawn spawns with a mount is 40% for tribals and 20% for non-tribals. These chances can be configured in the mod options. 
- Enemy pawns can only mount animals allowed in the mod options. The mounts they use will depend on the environment in which they attack. 
- Fixed issue that sometimes causes mounts to teleport when mounting is interrupted. 
		</content>
	</HugsLib.UpdateFeatureDef>
	<HugsLib.UpdateFeatureDef ParentName="UpdateFeatureBase">
		<defName>BattleMounts_0_18_4</defName>
		<assemblyVersion>0.18.4</assemblyVersion>
		<content>Giddy-up Battle Mounts has been updated with the following changes: 
- Spawning algorithm is improved for enemy mounts taking into account wildness of mounts and handling skill of pawns. Pawns with a high handling skill have a larger chance to spawn with rare mounts. 
- Enemy pawns now also spawn with animals not found in the biome in which they attack, and also with animals not occurring in the wild. The probability these mounts are used can be configured in the mod options. 
- Movement speed and accuracy penalty is affected by the animal handling skill of the pawn. If the rider's skill is higher than the skill required to tame the animal, a per-level bonus is applied, and otherwise a per-level penalty (configurable in the mod options). 
- Enemy mounts that lose their rider, will now become wild animals, making them tameable. If enemy pawns flee, they will now do so on their mount. 
		</content>
	</HugsLib.UpdateFeatureDef>
</Defs>