<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<ModMetaData>
	<name>UN-Colony [1.2]</name>
	<packageId>Sadjuuk.UNColony</packageId>
	<author>Sadjuuk</author>
	<supportedVersions>
		<li>1.4</li>
	</supportedVersions>
	<modDependencies/>
	<loadAfter/>
	<description>UN-Colony V1.2
		This mod adds many things to build a new kind of colony with new Walls, Furnitures, FLoors, Lights, Temperature Devices etc..
		It adds no new mecanics, only new items, receipes, building and textures. 9 researchs are also added.
		Warning : This mod is not compatible with its previous versions. The previous item management has been removed.
		For the moment this mod adds :
		FURNITURES :
		Hospital :
		-&gt; 4 types of Medical beds and Operating Table
		-&gt; 6 Upgrades : Pharmacies, Tending Tools, Surgery Lights, Wall Monitor
		-&gt; 1 Emergency Stretcher (3kg, useful for Combat Extended)
		Bedroom :
		-&gt; 3 types of beds, simple and double (Tribes, Ancient style and Industrial)
		-&gt; 9 Upgrades (Nightstand, Wardrobe, Steel Chest, Lockers, Small Steel Tables..)
		Others :
		-&gt; Wall Lights, Spots,  Floor Lights and Street Lights
		-&gt; Heaters, Wall Vents, Fan, Cooler
		-&gt; Tables and Chairs (Tribes, Ancient style and Industrial, Glass, Plasteel..)
		-&gt; Flags and banners
		INDUSTRY :
		Laboratory :
		-&gt; 3 types of research bench (Tribes, Ancient style and Industrial)
		-&gt; 9 Upgrades (Research library, Blueprint Table, Archival Cabinet, Computer Installation..)
		Generators :
		-&gt; 3 Portable generators (2 chemfuel, 1 hydrogen Fuel Cell)
		-&gt; 6 chemfuel generators (1500W to 18000W)
		-&gt; 1 rustic wood generator
		Production :
		-&gt; 1 Silicon Extractor producing Concrete and Glass from stone chunks
		-&gt; 1 Chemfuel Refinery with upgrades (Fuel Tanks, Cracking Unit, Hydrolyzer)
		-&gt; 2 new chemfuel recipes : Chemfuel from Hay and Chemfuel from corps
		-&gt; 5 types of storage and pallets
		BUILDING :
		-&gt; 4 types of walls and Embrassures (Wooden, Concrete, Armored, Plasteel)
		-&gt; 8 types of Doors and Autodoors (Wooden, Steel, Armored, Plasteel)
		-&gt; 16 types or colors of Floor (Wooden, Concrete, Asphalt, Resin Floor)
		-&gt; 4 types of Fences (Wooden, Glass, Concrete, Metal Grid)
		-&gt; 3 types of Paint (Lines, Arrows, Zebra)
		Notes :
		-&gt; Warning this mod is a completely revised version and is not compatible with the old ones of UN-Colony or UN-Furniture
		-&gt; I use Realistic Darkness and Combat Extended, it can have an impact on how the lights and wall's HP are set
		-&gt; Feel free to make your suggestions for additions or adjustments
		-&gt; A big thanks to Mlie for his work on previous versions and on all the Mlie's resurrected mods !
		Hope you will enjoy !
			</description>
</ModMetaData>