<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<LanguageData>

  <FT_TurretAA.label>Anti-Air gun</FT_TurretAA.label>
  <FT_TurretAA.description>A manned autocannon that launches solid metal bullets. Useful for attacking aerial targets or groups of enemies in the field.</FT_TurretAA.description>

  <FT_Gun_TurretAA.label>Anti-Air autocannon</FT_Gun_TurretAA.label>
  <FT_Gun_TurretAA.description>A manned autocannon that launches solid metal bullets. Useful for attacking aerial targets or groups of enemies in the field.</FT_Gun_TurretAA.description>

  <FT_TurretQuadAA.label>Quad Anti Air Gun</FT_TurretQuadAA.label>
  <FT_TurretQuadAA.description>A manned autocannon that launches solid metal bullets.It is rapid fired makes it useful for attacking aerial target or enemies in the field.</FT_TurretQuadAA.description>

  <FT_Gun_TurretQuadAA.label>Quad Anti Air cannon</FT_Gun_TurretQuadAA.label>
  <FT_Gun_TurretQuadAA.description>An Quad mounted Autocannon designed to defend the area of skies, but also a nice weapon for ground targets.</FT_Gun_TurretQuadAA.description>

  <FT_Bullet_AAShell.label>uranium APT shell</FT_Bullet_AAShell.label>

  <FT_TurretAT.label>Anti-Tank gun</FT_TurretAT.label>
  <FT_TurretAT.description>A manned cannon that fires solid metal shells. It's accuracy and armor penetration makes it ideal against heavily armored targets.</FT_TurretAT.description>

  <FT_Gun_TurretAT.label>Anti-Tank cannon</FT_Gun_TurretAT.label>
  <FT_Gun_TurretAT.description>A manned cannon that fires solid metal shells. It's accuracy and armor penetration make it ideal against heavily armored targets.</FT_Gun_TurretAT.description>

  <FT_Bullet_ATShell.label>uranium AP shell</FT_Bullet_ATShell.label>

  <FT_Turret_Mortar.label>infantry mortar</FT_Turret_Mortar.label>
  <FT_Turret_Mortar.description>A light-weight mortar that launches all kinds of shells. A simplified, faster, but inaccurate design, useful for attacking large static fortifications rather than groups of enemies in the field.</FT_Turret_Mortar.description>

  <FT_Artillery_Mortar.label>mortar</FT_Artillery_Mortar.label>
  <FT_Artillery_Mortar.description>Mortar launcher. Lobs bombs over walls. Very inaccurate but long-ranged.</FT_Artillery_Mortar.description>

  <FT_Maxim4M.label>Quad machine gun</FT_Maxim4M.label>
  <FT_Maxim4M.description>Four machine guns mounted on a tripod. Must be manned to operate. Requires steel to refurbish its barrels after heavy use.</FT_Maxim4M.description>

  <FT_Gun_QuadMG.label>4 machine guns</FT_Gun_QuadMG.label>
  <FT_Gun_QuadMG.description>What is better than a machine gun? Four of them.</FT_Gun_QuadMG.description>

  <FT_AutoCannon.label>Autocannon</FT_AutoCannon.label>
  <FT_AutoCannon.description>A tripod with an autocannon mounted on top. Must be manned to operate. Requires steel to refurbish its barrels after heavy use.</FT_AutoCannon.description>

  <FT_Gun_Autocannon.label>autocannon</FT_Gun_Autocannon.label>
  <FT_Gun_Autocannon.description>A self-loading large-bore cannon designed to be attached to a turret.</FT_Gun_Autocannon.description>

  <FT_RecoillessGun.label>Recoilless gun</FT_RecoillessGun.label>
  <FT_RecoillessGun.description>A tripod with recoilless rifle mounted on top. Must be manned to operate. Requires a replacement reinforced barrel after heavy use. Warranty void if used indoors.</FT_RecoillessGun.description>

  <FT_Gun_Recoilless.label>Recoilless cannon</FT_Gun_Recoilless.label>
  <FT_Gun_Recoilless.description>A gun with no recoil. Amazing!</FT_Gun_Recoilless.description>


</LanguageData>