<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" ?>
<LanguageData>
	<!-- settings -->
	<rim73_settings>Optimisations settings</rim73_settings>
	<rim73_settings_experimental>Experimental optimisations</rim73_settings_experimental>
	<rim73_settings_misc>Miscellaneous</rim73_settings_misc>
	
	<rim73_hediff>Enable hediff optimisations</rim73_hediff>
	<rim73_mood>Enable mood optimisations</rim73_mood>
	<rim73_needs>Enable needs optimisations</rim73_needs>
	<rim73_pather>Enable pather optimisations</rim73_pather>
	<rim73_jobs>Enable jobs optimisations</rim73_jobs>
	<rim73_mindstate>Enable mindstate optimisations</rim73_mindstate>
	<rim73_regionCache>Enable pather Region Caching system (experimental)</rim73_regionCache>
	<rim73_enemiesNearbyCache>Enable enemies nearby caching system (experimental)</rim73_enemiesNearbyCache>
	<rim73_superSpeed>Enable Warp Speed</rim73_superSpeed>
	
	<rim73_hediff_note>This optimises the hediffs and health ticks by reducing time it takes and improving memory caching.</rim73_hediff_note>
	<rim73_mood_note>Enables mood optimisations, this reduces unecessary checks.</rim73_mood_note>
	<rim73_needs_note>Enable needs optimisations by reducing the amount of checks in a second.</rim73_needs_note>
	<rim73_pather_note>Enable pather optimisations by preventing pawns to tick if there's someone blocking their path, they will go into "pathing sleep" unless they get attacked.</rim73_pather_note>
	<rim73_jobs_note>Enable jobs optimisations by reducing checks to nil for enemies and reducing them for pawns.</rim73_jobs_note>
	<rim73_mindstate_note>Enable Mindstate optimisations, this changes the way we calculate interactions per day.</rim73_mindstate_note>
	<rim73_regionCache_note>Enables the Region Caching System which makes it so that we don't update the region system unless the pawn has actually changed region.</rim73_regionCache_note>
	<rim73_enemiesNearbyCache_note>Enables Caching for Enemies nearby, meaning if one pawn of a group of raider is close to an enemy, all the others will consider it the case, without actually having to scan for nearby enemies.</rim73_enemiesNearbyCache_note>
	<rim73_superSpeed_note>Enables Super Warp Speed and on speed 4 reach up to 9000 ticks per second. WARNING: this is fast. Requires reload to take effect. If you're using SmartSpeed mod, this setting doesn't need reloading and the speed is limited to 1200 ticks.</rim73_superSpeed_note>
	
</LanguageData>