<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" ?>
<Defs>
	<ParagonWiki.Wiki.TutorialDef>
		<defName>CultureSystem</defName>
		<label>Culture system</label>
		<description>Description of the culture system</description>
		<text>
A culture system was introduced to encourage the player to leave their colony.
Culture is required mainly for research as an additional requirement.

The current amount of culture can be seen by opening the research window.
{Image(path="Core/Tutorials/CultureSystem/1", size="(500, 300)")}

Culture can be obtained in different ways:
- Rituals in ideology;
- Conversion of other pawns to your ideology;
- Obtaining psi-connection through the tree;
- Domestication of animals in the presence of the trait "animate animals" or "cattle breeding";

The most extensive and universal way to obtain culture is the construction of cultural buildings.
To build such a structure, you will need to create a drawing in the architectural table.
Drawings of varying complexity can be created in different architectural tables. For example, in primitive.
{Hyperlink(def="PrimitiveArchitecturalTable", defType="ThingDef")}

In the architecture window, you can select an object, read its description and what it does.
{Image(path="Core/Tutorials/CultureSystem/2", size="(520, 400)", expand="true", expandSizeMult="1.8")}

Please note that different architectural tables require different resources to generate a blueprint.

The amount of resources indicated in the window is the standard. The total amount depends on the "Brainwork" skill.
The higher the skill, the closer the final value will be to the standard.

When the drawing is ready, assemble the caravan and load the created drawing into it.
Then, find a suitable location for your building, select a caravan, "Create Object".
{Image(path="Core/Tutorials/CultureSystem/3", size="(500, 300)")}

Your item will be placed in the appropriate category. Select it, its requirements are met, the construction window will appear.
{Image(path="Core/Tutorials/CultureSystem/4", size="(500, 400)")}

Your object will be displayed on the map. The amount of resources for construction will be displayed in his description.
Equip the caravan with the necessary resources, and using RMB on the structure, click "Bring resources".

When all resources are delivered, you will need to send workers. To do this, use the "Send colonists to the construction site" command.
The progress of construction can be seen in the description of the building.
		</text>
		<wikiCategoryDef>Tutorial_Main</wikiCategoryDef>
	</ParagonWiki.Wiki.TutorialDef>
	
	
</Defs>