<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" ?>
<Defs>
	<ParagonWiki.Wiki.TutorialDef>
		<defName>FoodSystem</defName>
		<label>Food system</label>
		<description>Description and recommendations for the new food system</description>
		<text>
In the mod implemented an expanded food system, which includes 4 new types of needs:
- fats
- proteins
- carbohydrates
- vitamins
{Image(path="Core/Tutorials/FoodSystem/1", size="(227, 180)", expand="true", expandSizeMult="1.5")}

Each parameter has its own effect on the colonist, reducing the overall speed of work, mood.
Different plants and meat have their own showed saturation with these substances. To meet all your needs, you just need to have in your diet plants and meat in an acceptable amount.

We have created a very wide and varied system for creating dishes.
You can combine any ingredients to create your own dish, but banana and cucumber soup is unlikely to be delicious.

Taste is the mood equivalent of eating your food.
Each type of dish has a different effect on the values ​​​​of proteins, fats, carbohydrates, vitamins and taste in it.
You can create something simple, or take the time to produce really delicious food. The choice is yours.

{Image(path="Core/Tutorials/FoodSystem/2", size="(600, 470)")}

The creation of dishes takes place in:
{Hyperlink(def="CookingRecipeTable", defType="ThingDef")}

To create your own recipe, select the workbench, and open the "Recipes" tab and select "Create Recipe".
The recipe window consists of 3 parts:
- Left: dish template
- Center: dish setting
- Right: ingredient selection

A dish can have mandatory slots marked with a white outline. These slots must be filled.

{Image(path="Core/Tutorials/FoodSystem/3", size="(600, 470)")}
	
After filling in the ingredients, it remains to enter the name and descriptions, and click "Create Recipe".

The created recipe can be created in the field, allowing you to create the selected type of dish.
For example, you won't be able to create soup over a campfire, but you can in a cauldron or stovetop.
		</text>
		<wikiCategoryDef>Tutorial_Main</wikiCategoryDef>
	</ParagonWiki.Wiki.TutorialDef>
	
	
</Defs>