<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" ?>
<Defs>
	<ParagonWiki.Wiki.TutorialDef>
		<defName>Oil</defName>
		<label>Oil</label>
		<description>Description of the oil system</description>
		<text>
The process of oil extraction and processing is divided into several stages.


The first step before obtaining and processing oil is to produce ethanol through fermentation.
{Hyperlink(def="Chemfuel", defType="ThingDef")}
{Hyperlink(def="BiofuelRefinery", defType="ThingDef")}
Once you are ready, you can start pumping and processing oil.


To start production, it is enough to install an oil rig and a storage facility.
The refining process involves distilling oil through distillation columns. All this happens automatically, but requires a lot of water.
{Hyperlink(def="OilWell", defType="ThingDef")}
{Hyperlink(def="OilStorage", defType="ThingDef")}


First, the oil is broken down into fuel oil and middle oil. At the first stages, fuel oil cannot be disposed of or processed, so stock up on storage facilities or prepare a place for drainage.
{Hyperlink(def="DistillationColumnI", defType="ThingDef")}
{Hyperlink(def="MediumOil", defType="ProjectParagon.Core.Things.PipeTypeDef")}
{Hyperlink(def="HeavyOil", defType="ProjectParagon.Core.Things.PipeTypeDef")}


Then, the middle fraction of oil can be distilled into diesel fuel and obtain the light fraction of oil as a by-product. At the first stages, it will also not be possible to use the light fraction.
{Hyperlink(def="DistillationColumnII", defType="ThingDef")}
{Hyperlink(def="LightOil", defType="ProjectParagon.Core.Things.PipeTypeDef")}
{Hyperlink(def="Diesel", defType="ProjectParagon.Core.Things.PipeTypeDef")}


As you learn more technologies, you will be able to process fuel oil into diesel fuel and the light fraction into naphtha. Naphtha in turn is used as an ingredient in subsequent oil industry crafts.
{Hyperlink(def="DistillationColumnIII", defType="ThingDef")}
{Hyperlink(def="GasChamber", defType="ThingDef")}
{Hyperlink(def="Diesel", defType="ProjectParagon.Core.Things.PipeTypeDef")}
{Hyperlink(def="Naphtha", defType="ProjectParagon.Core.Things.PipeTypeDef")}



Visual diagram of the complete processing cycle:
{Image(path="Core/Tutorials/Oil/1", size="(510, 286)", expand="true", expandSizeMult="1.8")}
		</text>
		<wikiCategoryDef>Tutorial_Production</wikiCategoryDef>
	</ParagonWiki.Wiki.TutorialDef>
</Defs>