<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" ?>
<Defs>
	<ParagonWiki.Wiki.TutorialDef>
		<defName>OreMining</defName>
		<label>Ore mining</label>
		<description>Description of the mining system</description>
		<text>
Development in the assembly requires a large amount of resources, but how to get them?

Resources on the surface of the planet
There are several ways. Let's start with the simplest thing - the resources on the surface of your map.
Most of the resources that will be required for initial development are contained on the surface of the planet and access to them is quite simple.
However, pay attention to the biome. Some biomes are particularly rich in one type of ore and lack another. Additionally, the biome affects the richness of the ore.

Information about this can be found on the page of any biome:
{Hyperlink(def="Biome_SaltDesert", defType="BiomeDef")}

In addition, each ore contains all the important information about itself:
{Hyperlink(def="MineableHematiteOre", defType="ThingDef")}


What is ore wealth?
Ore richness determines how much resource each deposit contains. There are 3 gradations in total - depleted, regular and enriched.


What is the depth of the ore?
Ore depth determines how deep the ore lies. Mines and drilling rigs have depth limits that may prevent some particularly deep minerals from being recovered.


Underground deposits
The second, more advanced method is exploration and mining of underground ore.
This will be quite a challenge at first. You can build your first underground mines during the Middle Ages.
To understand approximately where it is worth building a mine, conduct a reconnaissance of the area (Projects -> terraforming)
{Image(path="Core/Tutorials/OreMining/1", size="(510, 372)", expand="true", expandSizeMult="1.8")}
Additionally, ore stalagmites on the surface can give you clues as to where to look.
{Image(path="Core/Tutorials/OreMining/2", size="(510, 485)")}


Meaningful drilling
A new step will be the targeted exploration of underground deposits using the power of science.
{Hyperlink(def="SeismicScanner", defType="ThingDef")}

Using scanning, you can understand where to install mining installations that will operate autonomously.
{Hyperlink(def="SteamDrill", defType="ThingDef")}
{Image(path="Core/Tutorials/OreMining/3", size="(510, 535)")}
		</text>
		<wikiCategoryDef>Tutorial_Production</wikiCategoryDef>
	</ParagonWiki.Wiki.TutorialDef>
</Defs>